Collection of Motion Picture Pressbooks PASC.0248
UCLA Library Special Collections
Collection of Motion Picture Pressbooks
1935-circa 1980s
UCLA Library Special Collections
PASC.0248
10.0 Linear Feet (6 boxes and 13 flat boxes)
Collection consists of motion picture pressbooks dating from 1935 to ca. 1980s.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9946689263606533
Scope and Content
Collection consists of motion picture pressbooks dating from 1935 to ca. 1980s. The collection primarily represents American films produced by companies including Columbia Pictures, Walt Disney, 20th Century Fox, MGM, Paramount, RKO, Universal, United Artists, and Warner Brothers.
Organization and Arrangement
The press kits are arranged alphabetically by film title.
Advertising -- Motion pictures -- Archives.; Pressbooks.
- 2001: A Space Odyssey, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- 5 Fingers of Death, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- 7 Women, no date (Box 22, Folder 4)
- 8th Day of the Week (The), no date (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Abdication (The), no date (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Abduction, no date (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Abominable Dr. Phibes (The), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Absent-Minded Professor (The), no date (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Ace High, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Across 110th Street, no date (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Act Of Vengeance, no date (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Act One, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Ada, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Adam and Eve/Go on a Spree, no date (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Adios, Sabata, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Advance to the Rear, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Adventures of Huckleberry Finn (The), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Africa- Texas Style, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- African Lion (The), 1955 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- African Queen (The), no date (Box 13, Folder 1)
- After the Fox, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Agony And The Ecstasy (The), no date (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Alcatraz Island, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Alias Jesse James, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Alice in Wonderland, no date (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Alien, no date (Box 9, Folder 2)
- All in a Night's Work, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- All the President's Men, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  Scope and Contents
  Folder 44 contains 4 audiocassettes.
- Aloha, Bobby and Rose, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Aloha, Bobby and Rose, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Amarcord, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Ambush Bay, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- America America, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- An Unmarried Woman, no date (Box 4, Folder 1)
- And Justice For All, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Anderson Tapes (The), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Andy Hardy Comes Home, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Angry Breed (The), 1968 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Animal World (The), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Aparajito, no date (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Aristocats, no date (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Assassination Bureau (The), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- At Gunpoint, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- At Long Last Love, no date (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Atomic Submarine (The), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Attack of the 50 ft Woman, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Avalanche, no date (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Awful Truth (The), no date (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Baby Face Morgan, no date (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Bad Girls Don't Cry, no date (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Bambi, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Bambi, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Barry Lyndon, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Bat (The), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Battle For The Planet Of The Apes, no date (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Battle of the Bulge, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Battling Mason, no date (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Baxter!, no date (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Bear (The), no date (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Beau Geste, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Bed and Board, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Bedford Incident (The), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Bedknobs and Broomsticks, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Being There, 1979. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Being There, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Belle de Jour, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Beneath The Planet Of The Apes, no date (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Best Years of our Lives (The), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Between the Lines, no date (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Beware of Children, no date (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Big Bad Mama, no date (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Big Bounce (The), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Big House for Girls (The) (also known as The Silver Lining), 1932 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Big Red, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Big Zapper, no date (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Billy Jack, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Billy the Kid Outlawed, no date (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Billy the Kid's Gun Justice, no date (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Bimbo the Great, no date (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Bird With the Crystal Plumage (The), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Birds Do It, Bees Do It, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Biscuit Eater (The), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Black Caesar, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Black Mama, White Mama, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Black Stallion (The), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Black Sunday, no date (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Black Swan (The), 1942 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Black Zoo, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Bless the Beasts and Children, no date (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Blood Money, no date (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Blood on the Arrow, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Blood Orgy of the She-Devils, no date (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Bloody Mama, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Blue Denim, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Blue Money, no date (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Blueprint for Robbery, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Boatniks (The), 1970 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Bob Hope's All Star Super Bowl Party, no date (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Bob Hope's Road To Hollywood, no date (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Bobby Deerfield, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Bon Voyage, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Bon Voyage, Charlie Brown, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Bone, no date (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Boom!, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Boots of Destiny, no date (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Bound for Glory, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Bourbon St. Shadows, no date (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Boy and His Dog (A) A Boy and His Dog, no date (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Boyfriend (The), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Boys From Brazil (The), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Boys In The Band (The), 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Breaker! Breaker!, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Breakfast for Two, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Breakheart Pass, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Breaking Away, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Breaking Away, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Bride Wore Black (The), circa 1968 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Brides of Dracula, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Broken Melody (The), no date (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Brotherhood (The), 1968 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Bubble (The) Bubble (The), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Buckskin Lady (The), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Buddy Holly Story (The), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Buffalo Bill and the Indians, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Bugsy Malone, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Bunny Lake is Missing, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Burnt Offerings, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Burnt Wings, no date (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Butcher (The), no date (Box 2, Folder 2)
- C.C. and Company, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Caged Heat!, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- California Dreaming, no date (Box 1, Folder 15)
- California Suite, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Call of the Blood (The), no date (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Can Heironymus Merkin Ever Forget…, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Can-Can, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Candidate (The), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Candy, no date (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Can't Stop the Music, no date (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Capone, no date (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Capricorn One, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Captain is a Lady (The), no date (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Car Wash, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Carnal Knowledge, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Carnival Story, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Carny, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Carrie, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Castilian (The), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Cell 2455, Death Row, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Challenge For Robin Hood (A), no date (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Chamber of Horrors, no date (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Changeling (The), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Changeling (The), 1980 (Box Unknown container 917 for instance of Changeling (The))
- Charley - One - Eye, no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Charley and the Angel, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Charley Chan on Broadway, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Charley-One-Eye, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Chartroose Caboose, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Chastity, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Chato's Land, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Cheap Detective (The), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Cheech and Chong's Up In Smoke, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Cheyenne Autumn Trail (The), 1964 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Chicken Chronicles (The), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Children of Paradise, no date (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Children of Paradise, no date (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Children of the Wild (also known as Topa Topa), no date (Box 15, Folder 33)
- China Gate, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- China Syndrome (The), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Chinese Connection (The) (also known as Jingwu Men), no date (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Chloe in the Afternoon, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Cincinnati Kid (The), 1965 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Cinderella, no date (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Circus (The), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Cisco Pike, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Clarence, the Cross-Eyed Lion, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Close Encounters, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Coach, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Coal Miner's Daughter, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Cobweb (The), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Cocaine Cowboys, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- College days (also known as Zis Boom Bah), no date (Box 17, Folder 3)
- COLUSSUS The Forbin Project, no date (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Coma, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Comes a Horseman, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Coming Home, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Conduct Unbecoming, no date (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Confessions of an Opium Eater, no date (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Conquest Of The Planet Of The Apes, no date (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Conquest of the The Planet of The Apes, no date (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Contract (The), no date (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Conversation (The), no date (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Coogan's Bluff, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Cops and Robbers, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Corpse Grinders (The), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Corrupt Ones (The), 1967 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Corvette Summer, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Count Yorga, Vampire, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Countess From Hong Kong (A), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Country Girl (The), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Courage of Black Beauty, no date (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Cousin Angelica, 1973. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Cranes are Flying (The), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Crazy Mama, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Cries and Whispers, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Crimson Circle (The), no date (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Critic's Choice, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Cromwell, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Crooked Romance (A), 1917 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Crooks Can't Win, no date (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Crossed Swords, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Cry of Battle, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Cry Tough, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Cupid's Knockout (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Daddy's Gone A Hunting, no date (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Damien Omen II, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Damnation Alley, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Damned (The), 1970 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Dangerous to Men, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Dark Star, no date (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Darker Than Amber, no date (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Darktown Strutters, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Daughter of the Tong, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Daugthers of Darkness (also known as Le Rouge Aux Levres), no date (Box 4, Folder 32)
- David Copperfield, no date (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Dawn of the Dead, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Day of the Locust (The), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Days of Heaven, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Deadly Mantis (The), no date (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Deadly Trap (The), no date (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Dealing, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Death in Venice, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Death on the Nile, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Death Race 2000, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Death Rides a Horse, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Death Sport, no date (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Deep (The), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Delinquent Parents, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Demon Seed, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Dersu Uzala (The) Hunter, no date (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Desert Commando, no date (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Design for Murder (also known as Trunk Crime), no date (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Despair, no date (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Destiny, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Destructors (The), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Devils (The), no date (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Die Laughing, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Different Story (A), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Dillinger, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Dirt Gang (The), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Dirty Harry, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Discreet Charm Of The Bourgeoisie (The), no date (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Divine Nymph (The), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Divorce, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Doc Savage, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Doctor Zhivago, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Doctor's Diary (A), 1937 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Dog Day Afternoon, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Doll Squad (The), 1973 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Don't Answer the Phone, no date (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Don't Just Stand There, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Down and Dirty, no date (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Down Liberty Road, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Dragoon Wells Massacre, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Drum, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Dumbo, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Dynasty, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Earthquake, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Eiger Sanction (The), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- El Diablo Rides, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Electric, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Elephant Walk, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Elliott, no date (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Elmer Gantry, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Emigrants (The), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Emil and the Detectives, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Emily, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Emmanuelle, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Empire Strikes Back (The), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- End (The), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- End Of The Road, no date (Box 1, Folder 30)
- End of the Trail, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Enforcer (The) (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Enforcer (The), no date (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Entertainer (The), 1960 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Equus, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Eraserhead, no date (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Escapade in Florence, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Escape From Fort Bravo, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Eugene Onegin, no date (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Every Which Way But Loose, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Evil (The), no date (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Executive Action, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Exquisite Thief (The), 1919 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Extreme Close-Up, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Eye for an Eye (A)n, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Eyes of Laura Mars, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Eyes of Laura Mars, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Fabulous World of Jules Verne (The)/Bimbo the Great, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Face to Face, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Faces, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Fahrenheit 451, no date (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Family Life, no date (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Family Plot, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Fantastic Animation Festival, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Fantastic Invasion of Planet Earth, no date (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Farewell my Lovely, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Fastbreak, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Fate is the Hunter, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Father Goose, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Federal Agent, no date (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Fellini Satyricon, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Fellini's Roma, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Female Bunch (The), no date (Box 20, Folder 42)
- Festival!, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Fiddler on the Roof, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Fiendish Plot of Dr. Fu Manchu (The), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Fiendish Plot of Dr. FuManchu (The), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Fifth Horseman is Fear (The), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Fight For Your Lady, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Fighting Gentleman (The), no date (Box 13, Folder 14)
- File of the Golden Goose (The), 1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Fillmore, no date (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Fire Sale, no date (Box 2, Folder 26)
- First Love, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- First Texan (The), 1956 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Fitzwilly, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Fixer (The), 1968 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Flesh and the Woman, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Flesh Gordon, no date (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Flight of the Doves, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Flower Drum Song/Imitation of Life, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Food Of The Gods (The), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Fools' Parade, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Foreign Agent, no date (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Fortuna, no date (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Fortune (The), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Fortune Cookie (The), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Foul Play, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Fountain of Love (The), no date (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Four Desperate Men, no date (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Four for the Morgue, no date (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Foxtrot, no date (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Frankenstein--1970, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Freebie and the Bean, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Frenzy, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Frenzy, no date (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Friday the 13th, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Friends, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Friends, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Fritz the Cat, no date (Box 2, Folder 27)
- From Hell to Victory (also known as De Dunquerque À La Victoire), no date (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Front Page (The), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Fun With Dick & Jane, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Funny Girl, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Funny Lady, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Fury (The), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Futureworld, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Gable and Lombard, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Gambler's Choice, no date (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Gambling Sex, no date (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Gang's All Here (The), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Gay Deceivers, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- General Della Rovere, no date (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Gentlman from Arizona (The), no date (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Gervaise, no date (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Get Out Your Handkerchiefs, no date (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Get Out Your Handkerchiefs, no date (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Girl Friends, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Girl In Black (A), no date (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Girl in Gold Boots (The), no date (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Girl With Ideas (A), no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Girlfriends, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Glacier Fox (The), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Gladiators (The), no date (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Glass Bottom Boat (The), 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Glenn Miller Story (The), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Gnome-Mobile (The), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Go For It, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Go Get 'Em Garringer, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Godfather Part II (The), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Godfather Part II (The), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Godspell, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Goin' Down the Road, no date (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Going My Way, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Golden Boys of the S.S., no date (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Golden Demon (also known as Konjiki Yasha), no date (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Golden Needles, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Golden Voyage of Sinbad (The), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Goldwyn Follies, no date (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Gone With the Wind, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Goodbye Girl (The), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Gospel According to St. Matthew (The), 1966 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Grace's Place, no date (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Graduate (The), no date (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Great Armored Car Swindle (The), no date (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Great Catherine, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Great Dictator (The), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Great Mail Robbery (The), no date (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Great Rupert (The), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Great Train Robbery (The), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Greyfriars Bobby, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Grissom Gang (The), no date (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Groupies, no date (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Gunfight at Comanche Creek, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Gunners and Guns, no date (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Gunpoint, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Guns of August (The), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Hail, Hero, no date (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Hallucination Generation, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Hamlet, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Hansel and Gretel, no date (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Happiest Millionaire (The), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Happy Birthday, Wanda June!, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Hard Boiled, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Hard Contract, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Hardcore, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Harlow, no date (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Having Wonderful Time, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Hawmps!, no date (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Hearse (The), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Heart is a Lonely Hunter (The), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Heart of New York (The), no date (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Heart Punch, no date (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Heartbreak Kid (The), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Hearts of the West, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Heidi, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Hell With Heroes (The), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Hello, Dolly!, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Her Husband Lies, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Here Come the Marines, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Hero Ain't Nothin' But a Sandwich (A), no date (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Hey, Let's Twist!, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- High Anxiety, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- High Plains Drifter, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- High Society, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- High Velocity, no date (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Hills Run Red (The), 1967 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Hindenburg (The), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Hit the Deck, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Hitchhikers (The), 1972 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Hitting a New High, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Hoffman, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Hold That Line, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Hollywood Boulevard, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Hollywood High, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Hollywood Hotel, no date (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Holster Full of Law (A), circa 1961 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Hombre, no date (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Honeymoon Killers (The), no date (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Hope (The), 1920 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Horizontal Lieutenant (The), 1962 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Horse Without A Head (The), no date (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Horsemen (The), 1971 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Hot Millions, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Hot Stuff, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Hound that Thought He Was a Raccoon (The), no date (Box 10, Folder 22)
- House by the Lake (The), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- House of Errors, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- House of Wax, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Housekeeper's Daughter (The), no date (Box 13, Folder 19)
- How the West Was Won, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Human Jungle (The), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Husbands, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Hustle, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- I Love You, Alice B. Toklas, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- I Married a Spy, no date (Box 14, Folder 2)
- I Never Promised You a Rose Garden, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- I Walk the Line, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Ice Castles, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Ice Station Zebra, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- If I Ever See You Again, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- If…, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Illustrated Man (The), 1969 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Imitation of Life, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Immortal Tales, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- In Hot Pursuit, no date (Box 8, Folder 46)
- In Like Flint, no date (Box 1, Folder 48)
- In Praise of Older Women, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- In the Money, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- In the Realm of the Senses, no date (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Incredible Journey (The), 1963 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Incredible Shrinking Man (The), no date (Box 6, Folder 20)